Indeed, quite interesting.
هذا مثير للاهتمام حقاً.
But this Paris polyphylla,
لكن هذه الزهرة ذات السبع أوراق
is it easy to collect?
هل يمكن الحصول عليها بسهولة؟
I've heard that when collecting it,
سمعت أنه عند جمعها
you need some luck,
قد تحتاج إلى بعض الحظ
because it grows in damp, deep mountains,
لأنها تنمو في الجبال العميقة الرطبة
making it extremely difficult to find.
ومن الصعب جداً العثور عليها.
Brother Chu, you even know about this.
الأخ تشو يعرف حتى هذا
You're truly knowledgeable.
يمكن القول إنك واسع المعرفة.
Come, Brother Chu,
هيا يا أخي تشو
I toast to you.
أشرب نخبك.
Brother Lin.
أخي لين.
That bodhi fruit waist pendant of yours
قلادة بوذا هذه التي ترتديها على خصرك
is quite unique.
مميزة حقاً
Where did you find it?
من أين حصلت عليها؟
I rarely see
نادراً ما رأيت
such exquisite craftsmanship.
حرفة بهذه الدقة والجمال.
My dear,
زوجتي
you haven't been drinking,
أنتِ لم تشربي الخمر
why do you seem drunk?
كيف أصبحتِ ثملة؟
Brother Lin.
أخي لين.
Your waist pendant is truly a fine piece.
قلادة خصرك هذه شيء رائع حقاً.
Only the wealthy or noble could wear such an item.
من يرتدي مثل هذا الشيء لابد أنه إما ثري أو نبيل.
It seems you're a hidden master.
يبدو أن الأخ لين شخص متميز يعيش في عزلة.
Brother Chu, you jest.
أخي تشو، أنت تمزح.
It was merely made by a friend,
إنها مجرد شيء صنعه صديق لي
originally as a token of love for my wife.
كانت في الأصل هدية حب لزوجتي.
My dear,
زوجتي
where is your pendant?
أين قلادة خصرك؟
Bring it out too.
أحضريها أيضاً.
I just remembered
تذكرت الآن
a few days ago when Mrs. Wang and I were moving vegetables
قبل بضعة أيام عندما كنت أنقل الخضار مع السيدة وانغ
I accidentally cut myself.
جرحت يدي بالخطأ
I've been quite busy these past couple of days
كنت مشغولة هذين اليومين
so I put it away
لذلك وضعته جانباً
with my clothes in the storage room.
مع الملابس في المخزن
I'll wear it again after things settle down.
سأرتديه مرة أخرى بعد أن أنتهي من هذه الأيام المزدحمة
You put it away?
وضعته جانباً؟
You haven't taken it off once in six years.
لم تبعديه عنك أبداً طوال هذه السنوات الست
I was afraid of losing it.
خشيت أن أفقده
You two enjoy your drinks
استمرا في الشرب
while I check on Ping'an.
سأذهب لأطمئن على بينغ آن
Brother Chu
أخي تشو
come, let's drink.
هيا نشرب معاً
Mrs. Lin
سيدة لين
my hand
يدي هذه
got hurt last night while I was washing clothes.
أصبتها بالأمس أثناء غسل الملابس
Mrs. Wang
السيدة وانغ
please rest for a while
استريحي قليلاً
I can carry this myself.
سأحمله ببطء بنفسي
I'm so sorry, Mrs. Lin.
آسفة يا سيدة لين
Your secret
سرك
doesn't matter anymore.
لم يعد مهماً الآن
Lin asked me to help you
أرسلني الأخ لين لمساعدتك
I'm not too late, am I?
هل وصلت في الوقت المناسب؟
My husband told me before he left
أخبرني زوجي قبل أن يغادر
you've arrived just in time.
لقد وصلت في الوقت المناسب تماماً
Mrs. Wang
السيدة وانغ
my husband needs me for something
زوجي لديه بعض الأمور
could you please watch the stall for me
هل يمكنك الاعتناء بالمتجر
while I go back home?
سأعود إلى المنزل للحظة
If there's something at home, you should hurry
إذا كان لديك أمر في المنزل فاذهبي بسرعة
I'll take care of everything here.
سأهتم بكل شيء هنا
Thank you.
شكراً لك
Go quickly.
هيا اذهبي
Lin Feng doesn't know your secret
لين فينغ لا يعرف سرك
but do you know
لكن هويته
who he really is?
هل تعرفينها؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد
Is Lin Feng keeping secrets from me too?
هل يخفي لين فينغ أسراراً عني أيضاً؟
I'm also curious
أنا أيضاً فضولي
what game you two are playing.
ما هي المسرحية التي يمثلها الزوجان
Lin Feng is no ordinary man
لين فينغ ليس شخصاً عادياً
he's the Chief Officer of the Shenwu Guard in Tongzhou
إنه قائد حرس شين وو في تونغتشو
currently investigating the iron ore smuggling case.
يحقق حالياً في قضية تهريب خام الحديد
Shi Jia from the blacksmith shop
شي جيا صاحب متجر الحدادة
is an important figure in a secret organization
هو شخصية مهمة في منظمة سرية
did you know that?
هل كنت تعرفين ذلك؟
The Shenwu Guard...
حرس شين وو؟
Smuggling iron ore
تهريب خام الحديد؟
though it violates imperial interests
رغم أنها تمس مصالح العائلة الملكية
isn't such a serious matter
لكنها ليست قضية كبيرة
why make such a big fuss about it?
لماذا كل هذه الضجة الكبيرة؟
The Shenwu Guard is our dynasty's military garrison
حرس شين وو هو مقر عسكري في مملكتنا
tasked with protecting the safety of Tongzhou region
يحمل مسؤولية حماية أمن منطقة تونغتشو
and preventing foreign invasions.
ومنع غزو الأعداء الخارجيين
Tongzhou, as a crucial transportation hub
تونغتشو باعتبارها طريقًا رئيسيًا مهمًا
and strategic location,
وموقعًا استراتيجيًا
holds great military significance.
لها أهمية عسكرية كبيرة
The Shenwu Guard must constantly patrol and remain vigilant,
يحتاج حرس شين وو إلى الدورية واليقظة باستمرار
staying alert at all times.
والبقاء متيقظين
Some people, to make a living,
بعض الناس من أجل العيش
sell small amounts of iron ore for some silver,
يبيعون كميات صغيرة من خام الحديد مقابل بعض الفضة
which isn't a serious matter.
وهذا ليس بالأمر الكبير
But smuggling large quantities of refined iron ore
لكن إذا كان تهريب كميات كبيرة من خام الحديد النقي
and sulfur ore,
وخام الكبريت
suggests their purpose
فإن هدفه
is not simply to earn some scattered silver
ليس مجرد الحصول على بعض الفضة
to get rich.
ليصبح ثريًا
Why are you telling me all this?
لماذا تخبرني بكل هذا؟
I don't understand.
أنا لا أفهم
Besides,
وأيضًا
how do you know so much?
كيف تعرف كل هذه المعلومات؟
My husband couldn't have told you these things.
زوجي لا يمكن أن يخبرك بهذه الأشياء
Could you and Lin Feng have met that night?
هل تعرفت على لين فنغ في تلك الليلة؟
He was one of the officials.
أحد رجال الشرطة كان هو
I was in a hurry to leave that day,
كنت مستعجلة ذلك اليوم
didn't want to cause trouble,
لم أرد إثارة المشاكل
and didn't see them clearly.
لم أتمكن من رؤيتهم بوضوح
But you,
لكنك
I saw you very clearly.
رأيتك بوضوح تام
Madam,
سيدتي
I know you don't want innocent people to die.
أعلم أنك لا تريدين قتل الأبرياء
You must know more about this matter.
أنت بالتأكيد تعرفين المزيد
I need your help for me and Brother Lin.
أحتاج مساعدتك لي وللأخ لين
The mastermind behind this,
الشخص وراء هذه القضية
who needs large quantities of refined iron and sulfur ore,
يحتاج كميات كبيرة من خام الحديد النقي وخام الكبريت
what exactly is he planning?
ما هي خطته بالضبط؟
Who are you really?
من أنت حقًا؟
Who sent you?
من أرسلك؟
What's your true purpose?
ما هو هدفك الحقيقي؟
Madam,
سيدتي
you can trust me.
يمكنك أن تثقي بي
I'm not your enemy,
أنا لست عدوك
and I'll keep your secrets.
سأحافظ على أسرارك
I was forced into this case,
لقد تورطت في هذه القضية رغمًا عني
and I need to prove my innocence.
أحتاج إلى إثبات براءتي
But I don't want to turn you in.
لكنني لا أريد الإبلاغ عنك
However, if more
لكن إذا تورط
innocent lives are at stake,
المزيد من الأبرياء
I ask you
أرجو منك سيدتي
to consider carefully.
أن تفكري مليًا
I have no other purpose
ليس لدي أي هدف آخر
than to find the mastermind, help Brother Lin solve the case,
أريد فقط العثور على المتآمر لمساعدة الأخ لين في حل القضية
and leave Tongzhou safely.
وأن أغادر تونغتشو بسلام
I never thought he would hide
لم أتوقع أنه أخفى عني
such a big secret from me.
سرًا بهذا الحجم
I had my suspicions
لقد شككت أيضًا
that he was keeping something from me.
أنه يخفي شيئًا عني
It must have been due to his official duties,
ربما كان مضطرًا بسبب منصبه الرسمي
so I didn't ask too many questions.
لذلك لم أسأل كثيرًا
Sister-in-law.
زوجة أخي
You go ahead first,
اذهبي أولاً
think carefully about what I said.
فكري جيداً فيما قلته لك
You third-rate characters,
أشخاص من الدرجة الثالثة
I'll take you in for a proper interrogation.
سأقبض عليكم وأستجوبكم جيداً
Let's see if you've got what it takes,
دعنا نرى إن كنت تملك القدرة على ذلك
Mr. Li.
سيد لي
There are still 10 days until delivery,
لا يزال أمامنا عشرة أيام حتى موعد التسليم
why have you come in person?
لماذا أتيت بنفسك؟
I happened to have business in Tongzhou,
كنت في تونغتشو لقضاء بعض الأعمال
so I stopped by to check if these carriages
فقررت المرور لأرى هذه العربات
are as good as you claimed.
إن كانت جيدة كما وصفها المدير
Rest assured,
لا تقلق
the craftsmanship you requested
هذه الحرفة التي طلبتها
can only be achieved by our team of craftsmen
لا يمكن لأحد سوى حرفيينا
within your delivery timeline.
إنجازها في الموعد المحدد
Mr. Li,
سيد لي
what are you planning to do
لماذا تطلب
with so many custom high-end carriages
صناعة كل هذه العربات الفاخرة
that you've ordered?
لنفسك؟ ما الغرض منها؟
You'll find out when the time comes.
ستعرف في حينها.
Rest assured,
اطمئن
it will definitely be delivered to you in ten days,
سأسلمها لك بعد عشرة أيام
without any delay.
ولن أتأخر أبداً.
This is a small token from me.
هذه هدية متواضعة مني.
Thank you, Mr. Li.
شكراً لك يا سيد لي.
Keep it to buy yourself a nice coffin.
احتفظ بها لتشتري لنفسك تابوتاً جيداً.
Burn this place down on delivery day,
أحرق هذا المكان يوم التسليم
and make sure it's clean.
ونظف كل شيء جيداً.
Master,
سيدي
Shi Jia has been killed.
تم قتل شي جيا.
The registry from his blacksmith shop
والسجل الذي كان في محل الحداد
has also been taken.
تم العثور عليه وأخذه أيضاً.
Fortunately, according to our plan,
لحسن الحظ، وفقاً للخطة التي وضعناها
the remaining transaction locations haven't been exposed.
لم يتم كشف مواقع الصفقات المتبقية.
The great gift Shi Jia mentioned in his letter to you
الهدية الكبيرة التي ذكرها شي جيا في رسالته إليك
refers to finding Suo Yun.
تشير إلى أنه وجد سو يون.
This Suo Yun
هذه سو يون
is the one who assassinated Shi Jia.
هي نفسها من قتلت شي جيا.
We've discovered she is
اكتشفنا أنها
the wife of Lin Feng, Captain of the Imperial Guard who's been investigating us.
زوجة لين فنغ، قائد حرس شنوو.
She's currently using the alias Yin Qingmo.
تستخدم الآن اسم ين تشينغ مو.
However, I wasn't able to obtain
لكنني لم أستطع الحصول على
evidence confirming her clan identity.
أدلة تثبت هويتها العائلية.
Have you seen how she uses her sword?
هل رأيتم كيف تستخدم سيفها؟
I heard that among Shi Jia's wounds,
سمعت أن جروح شي جيا
there was one fatal injury
كان هناك جرح قاتل
to his lung.
في رئته.
A few days ago, my men and I went to test her skills,
قبل بضعة أيام، ذهب رجالي لاختبارها
thinking we could subdue her.
وظننا أننا نستطيع السيطرة عليها.
Her swordsmanship is exceptional,
مهارتها بالسيف متفوقة
with no wasted moves.
ولا تضرب ضربة واحدة بلا هدف.
Do you know why she left a wound in the lung?
هل تعرفون لماذا تركت جرحاً في الرئة؟
Because it first pierces the opponent's lungs,
لأنه يطعن رئة الخصم أولاً
making them unable to scream even if they want to.
فيجعله يريد الصراخ لكنه لا يستطيع
This is the sword technique used by assassins who excel in stealth.
هذا أسلوب السيف الذي يستخدمه المتسللون في الاغتيال
Does she use her sword like this,
هل تستخدم سيفها هكذا
appearing to make a mistake before the second move,
وقبل الحركة الثانية تبدو كأنها ترتكب خطأً
then thrusting diagonally?
ثم تطعن بشكل مائل؟
The Golden Blade Sect doesn't keep incompetent and negligent people.
باب السيف الذهبي لا يحتفظ بالأشخاص المهملين والمقصرين
Tell those responsible for transporting the ore
أبلغ المسؤولين عن نقل المعادن
to use a new transaction location,
أن يستخدموا مكاناً جديداً للتبادل
and from today on, report only to me.
وأن يقدموا تقاريرهم لي وحدي من اليوم فصاعداً
Gotcha!
أمسكت بك!
Caught you!
لقد قبضت عليك!
Got you now.
سأمسك بك
There's nowhere to run.
لنرى إلى أين ستهرب الآن
Suoyun,
سوو يون
I hope you haven't forgotten
آمل أنك لم تنسي
that you're a Jurchen.
أنك من قبيلة جورتشن
My dear,
زوجتي العزيزة
my old leg injury is hurting a bit,
إصابة ساقي تؤلمني قليلاً
it might rain soon,
ربما ستمطر قريباً
I'll bring in the vegetables you hung out to dry.
سأذهب لأجمع الخضروات المنشورة للتجفيف
Let me do it.
دعني أفعلها.
You don't know which ones need to be spread out
أنت لا تعرف أيها يحتاج للنشر
and which ones need watering.
وأيها يحتاج للرش بالماء.
Then I'll help you carry these.
إذن سأساعدك في حمل هذه الأشياء.
My dear,
زوجتي،
Li Qiang says bamboo shoots will be going up in price soon,
سمعت من لي تشيانغ أن أسعار براعم الخيزران سترتفع قريباً،
should we get in on that business?
هل نشتري بعضها للمتاجرة؟
It's only because the Zhao family is buying so much.
هذا فقط لأن عائلة تشاو تشتري الكثير منها.
These common folks,
هؤلاء الناس العاديون،
they all just follow whatever the rich families do,
كلهم يقلدون العائلات الثرية،
it's just a passing trend.
إنها مجرد موجة عابرة.
You go rest first,
اذهب واسترح أولاً،
I'll be there soon.
سألحق بك حالاً.
My dear.
زوجتي.
Do you remember
هل تتذكرين
what I said the day we first met?
ما قلته لك يوم تعارفنا؟
We've been married for so long,
نحن زوجان منذ زمن طويل،
why bring this up now?
لماذا تتحدث عن هذه الأشياء؟
That day I said
قلت في ذلك اليوم
the past doesn't matter anymore,
إن الماضي لم يعد مهماً،
do you remember?
هل تتذكرين؟
What's wrong?
ماذا حدث؟
It's still the same now.
الأمر نفسه ينطبق الآن.
I should warn Brother Lin.
يجب أن أنبه الأخ لين.
Let's wait and see what happens.
من الأفضل أن نراقب الوضع.
If Yin Qingmo can deceive those people,
إذا استطاع ين تشينغ مو أن يخدع هؤلاء الناس،
and trick them again,
ويستطيع خداعهم مرة أخرى،
using their own strength against them would be better.
فسيكون من الأفضل استخدام قوتهم ضدهم.
But in that case,
ولكن في هذه الحالة،
should I tell him or not?
هل أخبره أم لا؟
Young master,
سيدي الصغير،
would you like some?
هل تريد أن تأكل؟
It's very sweet.
إنها حلوة جداً.
Would you like grandma to take you to buy a rattle drum?
هل تريد أن تأخذك الجدة لشراء طبلة صغيرة؟
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
It's all cold now. I'll heat it up for you.
الطعام بارد، سأسخنه لك.
Where is everyone?
أين الشخص؟
Look at this little girl,
انظر إلى هذه الفتاة الصغيرة،
she's quite brave.
إنها جريئة جداً.
You said it was your child.
تقول إنه طفلكما.
Do you know his name?
هل تعرف ما اسمه؟
Come with me to the magistrate's office
تعال معي إلى مقر الحكومة
and let's see if the child recognizes you.
لنرى إذا كان الطفل يعرفكم أم لا.
Getting nervous,
هل أنتم خائفون
afraid to go?
ولا تجرؤون على الذهاب؟
I've been watching you for a long time.
أنا أراقبكم منذ فترة طويلة.
You, woman,
أنتِ أيتها المرأة
hiding at the alley entrance every day to spy on the child.
تختبئين كل يوم عند مدخل الزقاق لتتلصصي على الطفل
I've long noticed your sinister intentions.
لقد اكتشفت نواياكم السيئة منذ زمن.
I'm going to stick my nose in this business.
وأنا سأتدخل في هذا الأمر بالتأكيد.
Could she be some kind of female hero?
هل هي فتاة محاربة؟
You little brat,
أيتها الفتاة الصغيرة
I advise you to mind your own business.
أنصحك ألا تتدخلي فيما لا يعنيك.
Look, this belongs to the Zhao family.
انظر، هذا شيء يخص عائلة تشاو.
Why don't we tie her up
ما رأيك أن نختطفها
and make more money?
ألن نربح المزيد من المال؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Don't come any closer!
لا تقترب مني!
I've already reported this to the authorities on my way here
لقد أبلغت السلطات في طريقي إلى هنا
and they'll be here any minute.
وسيصل رجال الحكومة في أي لحظة
Want to play the hero
تريد أن تكون البطل المنقذ
I'll oblige you.
سأحقق لك ذلك
Get him!
اضربوه!
Attack!
هجوم!
Look at this guy.
انظر إلى هذا الفتى
Do you know why I'm using a bamboo stick?
هل تعرف لماذا استخدمت عصا الخيزران؟
Because you need a dog-beating stick to beat a dog.
لأن ضرب الكلاب يتطلب عصا مخصصة لذلك.
I'm telling you, I knew they were bad news from the start.
أقول لك، كنت أعرف منذ البداية أنهم ليسوا أشخاصاً طيبين.
Yue'er,
يوه إر
please take Lele home now.
أسرعي وأعيدي لي لي إلى المنزل.
Yes, Miss.
حسناً يا آنستي
I'll wait for you at the shop.
سأنتظرك في المتجر إذن.
We're truly grateful to Miss Zhao and Master Lin
نحن ممتنون حقاً للآنسة تشاو والسيد لين
for their brave intervention
لشجاعتهما ومساعدتهما
that led to the capture of these traffickers.
في القبض على هؤلاء المتاجرين بالبشر.
No need for such formality.
لا داعي للشكر
My father always says
كان والدي يقول دائماً
that as merchants,
إن التاجر
we should do more to help our community.
يجب أن يفعل الخير لأهل بلدته.
From what those traffickers said,
من كلام تجار البشر هؤلاء
there must be more people behind them.
يبدو أن وراءهم المزيد من الأشخاص
Please don't let them off easily, sir,
أرجو من سيادتكم ألا تتساهلوا معهم
so our people can live in peace.
لإعادة الأمان للناس.
Of course.
بالطبع
Thank you both for your heroic assistance.
شكراً لمساعدتكما أيها الفارسان.
Do you know this child?
هل تعرفين هذا الطفل؟
Thank you for your help today, Master Lin,
شكراً للسيد لين على مساعدته اليوم،
preventing Lele from falling into the hands of those villains.
لمنع وقوع لي لي في أيدي الأشرار.
Lele is the child of the Xiuluo Fabric Shop owner.
لي لي هو ابن صاحب متجر الأقمشة المطرزة،
The shop has been very busy lately,
المتجر مزدحم بالأعمال مؤخراً،
so they've been unable to watch him closely.
لذلك أهملوا رعايته.
I often visit the shop to have clothes made,
أنا أذهب إلى المتجر كثيراً لصنع بعض الملابس،
so I naturally know Lele.
لذلك أعرف لي لي بالطبع.
Fortunately we found him in time,
لحسن الحظ اكتشفنا الأمر في الوقت المناسب،
otherwise the consequences would have been unthinkable.
وإلا لكانت العواقب وخيمة.
I see.
أفهم الآن.
Master Lin,
سيد لين البطل،
would you allow me to treat you to a meal
هل يمكنني دعوتك لتناول الطعام
to show my gratitude?
كتعبير عن شكري؟
You're too kind, Miss Zhao.
الآنسة تشاو، أنت متواضعة جداً.
Please, just call me Ruoting.
يمكنك أن تناديني رو تينغ فقط.
It felt wonderful to be a hero today.
الشعور بكوني بطلة اليوم كان رائعاً حقاً.
I wonder if you could teach me some martial arts,
هل يمكن للسيد لين أن يعلمني بعض فنون القتال،
so I can fight against evil alongside you?
لأتمكن من مساعدتك في معاقبة الأشرار؟
Though I don't know which noble family you're from,
رغم أنني لا أعرف من أي عائلة نبيلة أنت،
I can see that the officials
لكن من الواضح أن رجال الحكومة
treat you with great respect.
يعاملونك باحترام شديد.
Miss Zhao, you need not experience
الآنسة تشاو، ليس عليك أن تختبري
the dangers of the martial world.
مخاطر عالم الفروسية.
You should return home soon.
من الأفضل أن تعودي إلى المنزل مبكراً.
I must take my leave now.
أستأذن بالانصراف الآن.
Master Lin,
سيد لين البطل،
do you dislike people from official families?
هل أنت لا تحب رجال الحكومة؟
My surname isn't Lin,
أنا لست من عائلة لين،
I...
أنا...
Why did you lie?
لماذا تكذب؟
Miss Zhao.
آنسة تشاو.
Miss Ruoting, please don't misunderstand.
آنسة رو تينغ، لا تسيئي الفهم،
I just didn't want to cause any more trouble,
أنا فقط لا أريد المزيد من المتاعب،
and what I did today was actually a good deed,
وما فعلته اليوم كان عملاً طيباً،
so I had no intention of hiding anything.
لذلك لم أقصد إخفاء شيء بنية سيئة.
Then, hero,
أيها الفارس،
would you honestly tell me your name?
هل يمكنك إخباري باسمك الكريم بصدق؟
I am Chu Bufan.
أنا تشو بو فان.
I'm from Yingtian Prefecture,
أنا من ينغ تيان فو،
just arrived in Tongzhou a couple of days ago,
وصلت إلى تونغ تشو منذ يومين فقط،
and I hope Miss Ruoting can help me out.
أرجو منكِ آنسة رو تينغ أن ترعيني.
Sure.
حسناً.
If you need anything in the future, just let me know.
إذا احتجت أي شيء في المستقبل، أخبرني في أي وقت.
However, you just lied to me,
لكنك كذبت علي للتو،
and if you want my forgiveness,
إذا أردت أن أسامحك،
you'll have to accompany me to a nice restaurant.
فعليك أن ترافقني لتناول الطعام في مطعم جيد.
Alright then.
حسناً.
Wait a moment.
انتظر لحظة.
You truly are a great warrior,
حقاً أنت فارس عظيم،
eating like someone who has traveled far and wide.
هذه طريقة أكل لا يعرفها إلا من جاب البلاد شرقاً وغرباً.
I wouldn't call myself a great warrior,
أنا تشو لست فارساً عظيماً،
but I thought I hadn't revealed anything suspicious.
لكنني أعتقد أنني لم أظهر أي ثغرة،
How did you figure it out, Miss Ruoting?
لا أعرف كيف اكتشفتِ ذلك يا آنسة رو تينغ.
For the sake of this delicious grilled meat,
من أجل هذا اللحم المشوي اللذيذ،
would you tell me?
هل يمكنك إخباري؟
In storybooks, great warriors
الفرسان العظام في الروايات،
often conceal their true identities.
غالباً ما يخفون هوياتهم الحقيقية،
That was your first mistake.
هذه هي الثغرة الأولى.
Also,
وأيضاً،
when you were speaking with the guards today,
عندما كنت تتحدث مع حراس المحكمة اليوم،
you appeared calm on the surface,
رغم أنك بدوت هادئاً من الخارج،
but you made many subtle movements.
إلا أنك قمت بالعديد من الحركات الصغيرة.
You're quite observant, Miss Ruoting.
الآنسة رو تينغ ذات ملاحظة دقيقة،
Did you notice anything else?
هل لاحظتِ أشياء أخرى؟
You must be hiding some enormous secret.
لابد أنك تحمل سراً كبيراً جداً.